What did you think about the ride?
It was great, and apparently I've never been on live television before, but
apparently sometimes I don't watch the news, because I'm a kid, and apparently every time,
apparently Grandpa just gives me a remote after we watch the Powerball.
Tell me about the ride.
What did you think about the ride?
Well, it was great.
Why?
Because apparently you're spinning around, and apparently every time you get dizzy,
that's all you do is get dizzy.
Is it fun?
Yeah.
And I've never ever been on live television.
I've never ever been on live television.
Are you excited?
Yeah, and apparently I already went down the super slide.
When I went down the slide, I was scared half to death.
I just freak out.
Okay, okay.
What's his name?
Hi, honey.
Hold on, yep, hold on, I'm just going to ask him.
What's his name?
Noah.
Noah, what's your last name?
Dick Ritter.
How do you spell his last name?
Ritter, R-I-T-T-E-R.
Okay, where are you guys from?
Wilkes-Barre.
Wilkes-Barre, all right, buddy.
Good stuff.
Have fun.
There's a boy here looking for you.